National Council of Jewish Women, Washington, D.C. Section Collection 111
People's Archive, MLK Library
National Council of Jewish Women, Washington, D.C. Section Collection
1904-1942
People's Archive, MLK Library
Council of Jewish Women (U.S.)
111
0.25 Linear feet
1 Boxes
Arrangement
Processed without series.
Biographical / Historical
The stated objectives of the Washington, D.C. section of the Council of Jewish Women from Article II of the Council's constitution were "to bring about closer relations among Jewish Women; to furnish by an organic union a medium of communication and a means of prosecuting work of common interest; to further united efforts in behalf of Judaism by supplying means of study; to further united efforts in behalf of social reform by the application of the best philanthropic thought." The Washington Section included a study circle and a Mission School.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of yearbooks and programs.
Women; Yearbooks; Programs; Religion; Judaism; Associations, institutions, etc
- Series 1
  - Programs (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Program, 1904 (Item 1)
    - Program, 1904-1905 (Item 2)
    - Program, 1905-1906 (Item 3)
    - Program, 1940-1941 (Item 4)
    - Program, 1941-1942 (Item 5)
  - Yearbooks (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Yearbook, 1921-1922 (Item 1)
    - Yearbook, 1924-1925 (Item 2)
    - Yearbook, 1925-1926 (Item 3)
    - Yearbook, 1928-1929 (Item 4)
    - Yearbook, 1929-1930 (Item 5)